

{ 
  "quiz_two" : [
        {
          "id":1,
          "questionType": "complete_the_sentence",
          "questionText": "In java the ___________ data type is used to create a variable that should store text?",
          "answerFieldId": "answer_to_question",
          "correctAnswer": "string",
          "feedback": "String is a special data type that is used to store text."
        },
        {
            "id":2,
            "questionType" : "true_false",
            "questionText" : "Java and javascript are the same thing?",
            "options" : ["true", "false"],
            "correctAnswer" : "false",
            "feedback": "Java and Javascript are two different languages. Java is a language used to create software applications and applets, while Javascript is a scripting language used to create dynamic and interactive content on webpages."
        },
        {
           "id":3,
        "questionType": "multiple_choice",
        "questionText": "Which loop type would you use to repeat a task a set number of times?",
        "options": [
          "for",
          "switch",
          "while",
          "froot loops"],
        "correctAnswer": "for",
        "feedback": "The for loop is used to repeat a task a set number of times. The while loop repeats a segment of code an unknown number of times. Switch is a conditional statement, not a loop. Froot Loops are not a type of loop in java."
        },
        {
           "id":4,
        "questionType" : "true_false",
        "questionText": "The length() method can be used to find the length of a string?",
        "options" : ["true", "false"],
        "correctAnswer": "true",
         "feedback": "The length() is used to find the length of a string."
        },
        {
            "id":5,
        "questionType": "text_input",
        "questionText": "Which keyword is used to import a package from the Java API library?",
        "correctAnswer": "import",
        "answerFieldId": "answer_to_question",
        "feedback": "The import keyword is used to import a package, class or interface."
        },
        {
            "id":6,
        "questionType": "complete_the_sentence",
        "questionText": "The ______________ package is imported by default into Java programs?",
        "answerFieldId": "answer_to_question",
        "correctAnswer": "java.lang",
        "feedback": "The java.lang package provides classes that are fundamental to developing Java programs including the String class and the Math class."
        },
        {
           "id":7,
          "questionType": "multiple_choice",
          "questionText": "Which interface should be used by a Java program to be able to play audio files?",
          "options": [
            "ActionListener",
            "TextListener",
            "WindowListener",
            "AudioClip"],
          "correctAnswer": "AudioClip",
          "feedback": "The AudioClip interface is located in the java.applet package and can be used to play audio files."
        },
        {
            "id":8,
        "questionType": "text_input",
        "questionText": "What will be the output of this code? \n String aString = \"Crayons are great!\"; \n System.out.print(aString.charAt(8))",
        "answerFieldId": "answer_to_question",
        "correctAnswer": "a",
        "feedback": "The charAt() functions returns a character from a string at a specified index. In this case it is index 8 where the 'a' character is located."
        },
        {
           "id":9,
        "questionType": "multiple_choice",
        "questionText": "What is the name of the process by which two or more strings are joined together?",
        "options": [
          "Concatenation",
          "charAt",
          "Method",
          "Association"],
        "correctAnswer": "Concatenation",
        "feedback": "This is achieved with the use of the + operator. You can use concatenation to join two or more strings into one or print two or more strings together."
        },
        {
          "id":10,
        "questionType": "multiple_choice",
        "questionText": "Which of the following can be used to access the first element of an array named arrOne?",     
        "options": [
          "arrOne[2]",
          "arrOne[0]",
          "arrOne[3]",
          "arrOne[1]"],
        "correctAnswer": "arrOne[0]",
        "feedback": "Array indexes begin at 0, so the first element of an array is at index 0, the second element at index 1, and so on."

        },
        {
             "id":11,
        "questionType" : "true_false",
        "questionText": "main() method is used in every Java program?",
        "options" : ["true", "false"],
        "correctAnswer": "true",
        "feedback": "The main() method is what makes a Java program work. System.out.print() and System.out.println() are used to print text. There is no type() method in Java."
        },
        {
             "id":12,
        "questionType": "multiple_choice",
        "questionText": "Which package needs to be imported so that you can accept user input?",
        "options": [
          "java.util",
          "java.io",
          "java.awt",
          "java.awt.event"],
        "correctAnswer": "java.io",
        "feedback": "The java.io package provides classes for input and output for things like interaction with the user and reading and writing to files"
        },
        {
           "id":13,
        "questionType": "yes_no",
        "questionText": "The == operator can be used to compare two values?",
        "options": [
          "Yes",
          "No"],
        "correctAnswer": "Yes",
        "feedback": "The == operator can be used to compare two values."
        },
        {
           "id":14,
        "questionType": "multiple_choice",
        "questionText": "Which keyword would you use if you wanted a class to use an interface?",
        "options": [
          "main()",
          "new",
          "implements",
          "extends"],
        "correctAnswer": "implements",
        "feedback": "To use an interface, use the implements keyword with the name of the interface in the class declaration line in your code."
        },
        {
            "id":15,
        "questionType" : "true_false",
        "questionText": "In java # can be used to insert comments?",
        "options": ["True","False"],
        "correctAnswer": "False",
        "feedback": "In java // or /* are used to write comments."
        },
        {
             "id":16,
        "questionType": "complete_the_sentence",
        "questionText": "The _______ operator is used to multiply numbers",
        "answerFieldId": "answer_to_question",
        "correctAnswer": "*",
        "feedback": "The * is used to multiply numbers."
        },
        {
            "id":17,
        "questionType": "multiple_choice",
        "questionText": "Which of the following would you use to test a variable for five different values?",
        "options": [
          "else-if statement",
          "else statement",
          "switch statement",
          "if statement"],
        "correctAnswer": "switch statement",
        "feedback": "The switch statement is specifically designed to test one variable for a number of possible values."
        },
        {
            "id":18,
        "questionType": "multiple_choice",
        "questionText": "What is it called when an instance of a class is also an instance of its superclass?",
        "options": [
          "Instantiation",
          "Polymorphism",
          "Inheritance",
          "Encapsulation"],
        "correctAnswer": "Polymorphism",
        "feedback": "Polymorphism is when an instance of a class is also an instance of its superclass."
        },
        {
            "id":19,
        "questionType": "multiple_choice",
        "questionText": "Which of the following snippets of code can be used to instantiate an object?",
        "options": [
          "Class A = new AClass();",
          "AClass.newClass()",
          "AClass.instantiate();",
          "AClass.create();"],
        "correctAnswer": "Class A = new AClass();",
        "feedback": "Class A = new AClass(); creates an object named A which is an instance of the AClass class."
        },
        {
              "id": 20,
        "questionType": "multiple_choice",
        "questionText": "Which of the following GUI components can be included in a Java frame?",
        "options": [
          "textbox",
          "button",
          "label",
          "All of the above"],
        "correctAnswer": "All of the above",
        "feedback": "Textbox, label, button, images (and more) can all be included in a Java frame."
        }
    ]


}

